let questions = [{
  "question": "What animal lives only in China?",
  "answer": "Panda"
},
{
  "question": "What are the largest fish on the planet?",
  "answer": "Shark"
},
{
  "question": "What is the name of a bird with a bag under its beak?",
  "answer": "Pelican"
},
{
  "question": "What does the Earth's atmosphere mainly consist of?",
  "answer": "Nitrogen"
},
{
  "question": "What flower is the symbol of England?",
  "answer": "Rose"
},
{
  "question": "What flower can be called the national symbol of Russia??",
  "answer": "Chamomile"
},
{
  "question": "What is the central part of planet Earth?",
  "answer": "Core"
},
{
  "question": "Which ocean is the deepest?",
  "answer": "Pacific"
},
{
  "question": "What is the thickest tree on Earth?",
  "answer": "Baobab"
},
{
  "question": "Which country is the smallest on Earth?",
  "answer": "Vatican"
}
]